<?xml version='1.0'?>
<!DOCTYPE PISI SYSTEM 'http://www.pardus.org.tr/projeler/pisi/pisi-spec.dtd'>
<PISI>
    <Source>
        <Name>plasma-applet-icon-tasks</Name>
        <Homepage>http://kde-look.org/content/show.php/Icon+Tasks?content=144808</Homepage>
        <Packager>
            <Name>Alexey Ivanov</Name>
            <Email>alexey.ivanes@gmail.com</Email>
        </Packager>
        <License>GPL</License>
        <IsA>data</IsA>
        <PartOf>desktop.kde.addon</PartOf>
        <Summary>This is a modified version of the KDE taskbar, and taskmanager library.</Summary>
        <Description>The main change is to preserve the position of tasks and launchers. e.g. when a launcher is activated, the resultant task item appears in the same place in the taskbar as the launcher did.</Description>
        <Archive sha1sum="781763ebfab48e0ef4534ba8b3b74ddaff48d371" type="tarbz2">http://kde-apps.org/CONTENT/content-files/144808-plasma-icontasks-0.9.2.tar.bz2</Archive>
        <BuildDependencies>
            <Dependency>kdebase-workspace-devel</Dependency>
            <Dependency>kdelibs-devel</Dependency>
            <Dependency>libdbusmenu-qt-devel</Dependency>
        </BuildDependencies>
    </Source>
    <Package>
        <Name>plasma-applet-icon-tasks</Name>
        <RuntimeDependencies>
            <Dependency>kdebase-workspace</Dependency>
            <Dependency>kdelibs</Dependency>
            <Dependency>libdbusmenu-qt</Dependency>
            <Dependency>qt</Dependency>
        </RuntimeDependencies>
        <Files>
            <Path fileType="library">/usr/lib</Path>
            <Path fileType="data">/usr/share</Path>
        </Files>
    </Package>
    <History>
        <Update release="5">
            <Date>2012-02-11</Date>
            <Version>0.9.2</Version>
            <Comment>Version bump.</Comment>
            <Name>Marcin Bojara</Name>
            <Email>marcin.bojara@gmail.com</Email>
        </Update>
        <Update release="4">
            <Date>2011-10-26</Date>
            <Version>0.8.1</Version>
            <Comment>
                0.8.1
                =====
                1. Only show standard items in right click menu of tooltip.
                2. Use italic text for system-wide dock-manager plugins.
                3. Delete item delegate of dock plugins, to stop KWidgetItemDelegateEventListener logging so many warnings. This should not be required, but it keeps the library quiet...
                4. Hungarian translation - thanks to Kristóf Kiszel
                5. Turkish translation - thanks to Yavuz Ünver
                
                0.8.0
                =====
                1. Better, less hacky, way of placing newly created group where first task of group was. (And placing of task after group is closed).
                2. Vary size of drop indicator (16 to 32pixels) depending upon task item sizes.
                3. Italian translation - thanks to Giovanni Tedaldi
                4. Brazilian Portuguese translation - thanks to Luis Fernando Planella Gonzalez
                5. When drawing spinner for non-launcher task, draw task background and icon with 50% opacity.
                6. Reduce space taken by tasks in non-composited tooltips.
                7. Adjust size of popup menu (up to 512 pixels) based upon task's text.
                8. Fix duplicate items created when plasma-desktop is restarted and taskbar contains a task group.
                9. Restrict hue value of background colours to be between 196 and 224, likwise restrict saturation to be between 128 and 196. Improves contrast with icon.
                10. Move progressbar to the bottom of the icon - to give more space for indicators.
                11. Don't fade minimized tasks, fade the indicator instead.
                12. Allow larger indicators for larger tasks.
                13. If we have more the 1 recent document, place in a 'Recent Documents' menu.
                14. Parse ~/.recently-used.xbel and ~/.local/share/recently-used.xbel to obtain Gtk recent documents.
                15. Pase ~/.recently-used for LibreOffice recent documents.
                16. Only monitor the dbus service for DockManager helpers started by IconTasks.
                17. Better icon positioning.
                18. Clear DockManager and Unity menus when helper/application terminates.
                19. Alter DockManager plugin config page; remove filter, use item delegate to improve look of items, move details into information button.
                20. Add a 'Refresh' menu entry to main popup menu, to attempt to work-around ghost taskbar issues.
                21. To help with Firefox unity plugin, when unity API is enabled set the DESKTOP_SESSION env var to ubuntu.
                22. Draw progress fill at least 4pixels wide, so as to stop odd look at low progress.
            </Comment>
            <Name>Alexey Ivanov</Name>
            <Email>alexey.ivanes@gmail.com</Email>
        </Update>
        <Update release="3">
            <Date>2011-09-30</Date>
            <Version>0.2.0</Version>
            <Comment>
            1. For tooltips of task/group items, show [window icon][text][close icon] above each preview - instead of large icon and text below. Allow windows to be closed via close icon.
 			2. Add option to set task spacing - 0(default) to 50 pixels.
 			3. Add option to control if task frames should be rotated in vertical panels.
 			4. Add option to specify icon scale - 50% to 100%
 			5. Add option to control when tooltips are displayed; never, instant, after delay.
 			6. Remove 'Force rows' option.
 			7. Fix issue where if launcher was activated on one activity, when a new activity was activated the launcher would not appear.
 			8. Detect whan a window changes its window class/name. This happens with LibreOffice.
			9. Use screen size to determine how man windows can appear in tooltip - use multiple rows if necessary.
			10. Each time a task is associated/disassociated with a launcher, recehck whether it should be shown. Helps when the same app is started/closed on multiple	desktops/activities.
            </Comment>
            <Name>Alexey Ivanov</Name>
            <Email>alexey.ivanes@gmail.com</Email>
        </Update>
        <Update release="2">
            <Date>2011-08-30</Date>
            <Version>0.1.1</Version>
            <Comment>Fix KDE4.6 compile; rename lib directory to taskmanager, use quotes for taskmanager includes (so that local copy is found first), etc.</Comment>
            <Name>Alexey Ivanov</Name>
            <Email>alexey.ivanes@gmail.com</Email>
        </Update>
        <Update release="1">
            <Date>2011-08-29</Date>
            <Version>0.1.0</Version>
            <Comment>First release.</Comment>
            <Name>Alexey Ivanov</Name>
            <Email>alexey.ivanes@gmail.com</Email>
        </Update>
    </History>
</PISI>
